<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Database>
	<EnglishText>
		<!--Civ Unique Buildings-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_QUARTER_PUNIC_PORT_NAME">
			<Text>Punic Port</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_QUARTER_PUNIC_PORT_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>Carthaginian Unique Quarter. Created by constructing the Cothon and Dockyard in the same District. Increases the number of [icon:NOTIFICATION_DISCOVER_RESOURCE] Resources that may be assigned to this Settlement by 2.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_QUARTER_PUNIC_PORT_TOOLTIP">
			<Text>Increases the number of [icon:NOTIFICATION_DISCOVER_RESOURCE] Resources that may be assigned to this Settlement by 2.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_COTHON_NAME">
			<Text>Cothon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_COTHON_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>+2[icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production. +1[icon:YIELD_PRODUCTION] Production Adjacency for Coast, Navigable Rivers, and Wonders. Carthaginian Unique Production Building. Ageless. Can be purchased in Towns. Must be placed on Coast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_COTHON_TOOLTIP">
			<Text>Carthaginian Unique Production Building. Ageless. Can be purchased in Towns. Must be placed on Coast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_DOCKYARD_NAME">
			<Text>Dockyard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_DOCKYARD_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>+2[icon:YIELD_GOLD] Gold. +1[icon:YIELD_FOOD] Food Adjacency for Resources, Districts, and Wonders. Carthaginian Unique Gold Building. Ageless. Can be purchased in Towns. Must be placed on Coast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_DOCKYARD_TOOLTIP">
			<Text>Carthaginian Unique Gold Building. Ageless. Can be purchased in Towns. Must be placed on Coast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Wonders-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_WONDER_BYRSA_NAME">
			<Text>Byrsa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_WONDER_BYRSA_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>+2[icon:YIELD_GOLD] Gold. Trade Routes cannot be plundered. All tiles in this City that are adjacent to Coast and eligible for Walls receive a Wall. Must be placed adjacent to a Coast tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_WONDER_BYRSA_TOOLTIP">
			<Text>Trade Routes cannot be plundered. All tiles in this City that are adjacent to Coast and eligible for Walls receive a Wall. Must be placed adjacent to a Coast tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_QUOTE_WONDER_BYRSA">
			<Text>There are to be seen at this day certain ruins of the city walls.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_QUOTE_AUTHOR_WONDER_BYRSA">
			<Text>Leo Africanus</Text>
		</Row>
	</EnglishText>
</Database>